The year is 2048.
现在是2048年
Evolving technologies can no longer be regulated.
高端技术的发展已超出可控范围
Dangerous advancements forever alter the criminal landscape.
犯罪领域被某些危险性高的技术彻底改变
Police are not prepared.
警方措手不及
Law enforcement combats this corruption with a new line of defense.
执法人员引入了一队新的力量 来应对这严峻问题
But not all are created equal.
但所有成员的情况不尽相同
The idea behind the DRNs was to be as human as possible.
DRN的构想是尽可能地接近人类
They were based on a program called Synthetic Soul.
他们是基于一个叫人造灵魂的程序
That's one of the crazy ones.
这是里面最疯那个
- I'll lead you in? - Let's go.
- 我带你进去? - 走吧
Now all cops... human and manmade together...
现在 警方所有人员 人类和非人类一起
take on the battle to watch over us all.
开始了这场监管我们所有人的战争
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 机器之心 第一季第3集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 机器之心 第一季第3集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：光影
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：忘记保存就得从头翻ToT 校对：剥你皮 时间轴：光影
Charge at capacity.
电量已充满
Hey, James.
嘿 James
- Morning, Mr. Navarro. - How you doing?
- 早啊 Navarro先生 - 今儿怎么样啊?
Miss Miller.
Miller女士
Oh. James.
James
Left your key in the lock again.
钥匙又忘记拔了
Thank you. I swear my memory gets worse every day.
谢谢 记性一天比一天差了
I told you, I can have maintenance come in and switch those out for bio locks if you'd like.
不是跟你说过 我可以找人过来 给你换成生物锁
That's all right, I prefer the old-fashioned way.
没关系 我还是喜欢老式的
- I'm funny, I guess. - No, no, no, I like that.
- 很搞笑吧 - 不 没有 挺好的
Uh, this came to the security desk for you.
啊 这是有人放在安保那给你的
- Oh, thank you. - I got to get back to the desk.
- 哦 谢谢 - 我得回去啦
See you.
回见
Hi, can I help you?
你好 有什么可以为您做的吗?
- What's your name? - James.
- 你叫什么名字? - James
Let's go.
走吧
(SERVER ROOM)
(服务器室)
You know what I love best about you? Your punctuality.
知道我最欣赏你哪一点吗? 准时
What's that supposed to mean?
这话什么意思?
You're late and the car smells like olive oil.
你迟到了 还有 车里一股橄榄油味
Hold this... and this.
拿着这个 还有这个
What am I doing here?
这是在做什么?
You're heating my coffee.
加热我的咖啡
I like it hot.
我喜欢喝热的
It's best between 155 and 175 degrees.
咖啡在155到175度口感最好
Most people prefer it at 175.
大部分人都喜欢喝175度的
You like it at 165, and that's what it is.
你喜欢165度的 现在正好
You know how I like my coffee?
知道我喜欢喝什么样的咖啡吗?
Yes, I, unlike you, pay attention to details, like what time it is and what time
知道 你不注重细节 我跟你不同 我这人重细节 比如现在是什么时间啊
you're supposed to pick up your partner for shift.
哪个点去接搭档上班啊什么的
Oh, I pay attention to details, like you just put your finger in my coffee.
我也重细节 比如你刚把手指 放进我的咖啡里了
If you'd like, I could put it somewhere else.
你要是喜欢 我还可以放别的地方
Wa-Wa-Wait, go back.
等等 还是回去吧
- To where? - To when I didn't have a partner and I could drive to work in peace.
- 回哪里? - 回到我没有搭档 可以安静地开车上班时
I know you took my advice
我知道你听了我的建议
and used olive oil on your leg, John, and it works.
在假肢上用了橄榄油 John 有效果吧
You're just too stubborn to say thank you, but you're welcome.
你就是太拧 说不出谢谢 没事 不客气
I ate a salad... a Greek salad.
我吃了份沙拉 希腊式沙拉
At 10:00 a. m.?
上午10点?
Boy, you're some detective.
小子 你还真是侦探啊
Finally. Now you're talking.
你终于肯承认了啊
13 RAY. Possible 31. Homicide.
13R 疑似凶杀案
Body discovered at 4500 Crescent Av.
尸体在Crescent路4500号被发现
- That's three blocks away. - All right, let's go to work.
- 就在三个街区之外 - 好吧 开工
How long you been here?
你们来了多久了?
We just got here. There were no witnesses to the shooting.
刚到 没有人目击枪杀过程
The incident happened within the last 20 minutes.
案件大概发生在20分钟之前
- Who found him? - These two, and we've cordoned off the area.
- 尸体谁发现的? - 她俩 我们已经把这里封锁了
They killed the cameras.
他们击毁了摄像头
I think I can still access the archived footage.
我应该还能看到之前存储的影像
John...
John
They went up to the 25th floor.
他们去了25层
They shut down the elevator.
电梯被关闭了
Transmit that security footage to Maldonado,
把录像传给Maldonado
so we can try and I.D. these guys.
想办法确认这些人的身份
Officer Harrison, call for backup and begin evacuation protocols.
Harrison警官 先请求支援 然后执行疏散规程
- Yes, sir. - And be careful.
- 是 长官 - 小心点
- Perps are still in the building. - You got it.
- 匪徒可能还在楼里 - 明白
What's the plan?
你有什么计划?
I got no idea...
目前还没什么想法
but we got 25 floors to figure it out.
但是 还要爬25楼呢 慢慢想
Hand over the phone.
手机交出来
- Shut your mouth. - Hand it over.
- 把嘴闭上 - 交出来
- Stop talking. - Please don't hurt me.
- 都安静点 - 求你 别伤害我
- Let me see it... hey, hey. - ??? Let's go.
- 我看看 嘿 - 走了
I told you, you sit down.
说什么来着 给我坐下
Hello.
你好啊
What's your name?
你叫什么名字?
Oh, you, you don't know how to answer that, do you?
不知道怎么回答吗?
You're afraid if you answer, you'll get hurt, huh?
害怕一旦回答了 会受到伤害?
Well... the only way around that is...
其实 唯一可以避免受伤的办法
that you answer honestly.
就是老实回答
It's always the best policy.
诚实总是上上策
Jenna.
Jenna
Why don't you come and join me, Jenna?
跟我一起出来吧 Jenna
Yo.
嘿
- We can start now. - Cops are still in the lobby.
- 可以开始了 - 警察还在大厅呢
Well, that's their fault.
那就是他们的错了
It's time to get their attention.
该给他们提个醒了
Out of the way, out of the way.
让一下 让一下
Stay down.
都别慌
- Police. Keep moving. - This is not a drill.
- 警察 继续往前走 - 这不是演习
- What's going on? - Sir, we need you to keep moving, continuing out of the building.
- 发生什么事了? - 先生 继续往前走 走出大楼
- Go down the stairwell. - What's going on out there?
- 从楼梯下去 - 到底出什么事了啊?
- Out of the building, please. - Take the rest of the day off.
- 请尽快出楼 - 后半天就放个假吧
Move to the stairs, exit the back of the building.
往楼梯口走 走出大楼
- What's the update, Stahl? - It's the Sanderson building downtown.
- 什么情况 Stahl? - 是市区的Sanderson大楼
John's on the second floor ascending.
John在二楼 正往上去
Ascending? John!
上楼? John!
What's your status?
你们现在什么情况?
Dorian says the building is still structurally sound.
Dorian说这楼目前还算稳定
There's damage to the third and fourth emergency exits.
三四楼的紧急出口有些损毁
The southeast stairwell is also blocked.
东南边的楼梯口也被堵住了
Emergency personnel are getting people out by the second story.
紧急救援人员正在二楼疏散人群
John, do not ascend. Negative.
John 不要上楼 不行
Continue to direct the employees to the second floor
继续把人往二楼疏散
and go there yourself until we know what we're dealing with here.
然后原地待命 直到我们查明对方的情况
I know what we're dealing with.
对方的情况我知道啊
The assailants are still in the building. We're going after them.
匪徒还在楼里 我们马上去追查
Buy me some time. You should initiate the protocol.
帮我争取些时间吧 你快启用应对方案吧
Jam all comm signals coming in and out of the building,
对传入传出大楼的信号进行干扰
cut their communication, and get me some backup.
切断他们的通讯 再派些人来支援我
John, if we jam the signal, comms won't make it out of the building.
John 干扰信号的话 通讯信号无法传出
We won't be able to communicate.
我们就没办法通话了
Leave the building now.
立刻撤出大楼
There's... I can't...
还有...我不能...
What... do...
你说...什么...
Do you... Christmas.
什么...圣诞
Did you just hang up on Captain Maldonado?
你刚挂了Captain Maldonado的电话?
Yeah, boring conversation anyway.
嗯 反正也没啥好说的
I just love that you wear your insubordination like it's a virtue.
我太爱你不服从命令还以此为傲的样子了
- Did we evacuate the perimeter? - Per protocol, three-block radius.
- 周围都疏散过了吗? - 劫匪应对方案 范围三个街区
Yeah, this is Paul.
我是Paul
Lock down communications.
关闭通讯
- Initiate the jam. - Sequence initiated.
- 开始进行干扰 - 序列顺序启动
Okay, signal active. Switching to internal comms.
完毕 已激活 切换至内部通讯
They jammed us.
他们在干扰通讯
All external communications are blocked.
所有外部通讯都被阻止了
Law enforcement is nothing if not predictable.
这些执法人员的反应也太好预测了
Alpha team, take the north side.
A队 北边
Bravo team, take the rooftop.
B队 楼顶
Hold your fire until instructed.
原地候命
Clear.
安全
Any more thoughts on that plan? We're running out of floors, John.
想到什么计划没? 没几层楼了 John
Well, I thought backup would be here by now.
支援人员应该已经到了
Guess we just keep moving up.
我们只要继续往上走就好
Maybe there's another option.
或许还有别的选择
The entire air system is interconnected.
整栋楼的通风系统是相通的
We just have to make it to the 23rd floor.
我们爬到23楼
- There's an access door to the air system there that'll take us up to where these guys are. - See?
- 那有通风系统入口 我们从那去劫匪那 - 看到没?
Told you we'd come up with a plan.
早跟你说会想到办法的吧
What's with the disco face? Got something to tell me?
你脸怎么闪来闪去的 是不是跟我解释下?
Since the signals are now being jammed, every emergency call being placed in this building
信号遇到了干扰 所有从这栋楼打出的求救电话
(EMERGENCY RESPONSE REQUESTS) is bouncing back to me because they can't get out.
都转到了我这 因为信号传不出去
Answer the calls. We might get some information.
接吧 或许能得到些信息呢
Hello?
您好
Thnak God. I need police. I am in my office. There was an explosion.
感谢上帝 我需要警察帮忙 我现在在办公室 刚刚听到了爆炸声
Ma'am, it's okay. I understand. The police are already on their way.
女士 请放心 我知道了 警方已经出动了
Make your way down to the second floor.
请您下到二楼
- What are you doing? - In the Portuguese culture, it is proven
- 你在做什么啊? - 葡萄牙有研究发现 遇到紧急情况时
that people find a woman's voice more soothing in moments of crisis.
女性的声音更能让人感到安慰
- Hello? - Hello.
- 您好 - 你好
I'm Detective John Kennex.
我是John Kennex警探
I'm an automated police officer with a very difficult personality.
一名性格很奇怪的机器警员
- 911? - Please remain calm.
- 911吗? - 请保持冷静
I'm-I'm trapped with a gunman. Please help.
我被困住了 这有群拿着枪的男人 救救我
Everything's all right. Just take a breath.
不会有事的 你先调整下呼吸
What is your name?
你叫什么名字?
It's Paige.
Paige
Hi, Paige.
你好 Paige
- What can you tell me about the gunmen? - I don't know.
- 那个拿着枪的人现在什么情况? - 我不知道
They have my sister...
我妹妹在他们手上
and others.
其他人也在
Listen, Paige, I'm in the building.
听着 Paige 我就在楼里面
I need to ask you a few questions,
我有几个问题要问你
but first I need to know... are you safe?
但首先 我想确认一下 眼下你安全吗?
Are you out of harm's way?
没有危险吧?
I think so.
应该没有
- For now. - Okay, listen to me.
- 暂时没有 - 好 那你听我说
Where are you? What floor are you on?
你在哪呢? 在几楼?
I'm on the 25th floor.
我在25楼
I'm in the utility closet.
藏在储物柜里
Next face.
下一个
You, on your knees.
你 跪下
On your knees!
跪下!
Oh, no, no! Oh, God.
哦 不 上帝啊
Paige?
Paige?
Paige, what's happening?
Paige 发生什么事了?
They've shot him.
他们开枪把他打死了
Lou is dead.
Lou死了
Hey, dogface. Water.
小子 水
We got a body!
有具尸体!
(NO COPS STAY OUT) Keep those people back!
(外面的条子都撤走) 别让那些人靠近!
Those bastards. What do they want?
这些混蛋 他们到底想要什么?
Detective Paul, initiate hostage protocol.
Paul警探 启动人质救援方案
Send them the comm. Send them the comm!
把电话给他们 把电话给他们!
Get that drone in the air. We've got to start negotiating.
无人机升上去 得跟他们谈判
Comm's here.
电话来了
- What's your name? - Captain Maldonado.
- 怎么称呼? - Maldonado队长
And you are?
你是?
Well, I'd tell you, but I don't want to nullify your efforts.
本来想告诉你的 还是不浪费你的精力了
Now that we have your attention...
既然成功把你们的注意力吸引过来了
we have some demands.
我们就要提要求了
Paige, can you hold the phone up so I can hear what's going on?
Paige 能把手机往外放一点 让我听听里面的情况吗?
I really hate to throw out any more hostages.
我也不想再往下扔人质了
- Let's get down to brass tacks, huh? - What do you want?
- 还是说正经事吧 - 你们想要怎样?
First, get your snipers off the roof, and tell those men
首先 让你们的狙击手从楼顶撤走
you have assembled out front to stand down, and keep them away from the building,
让他们在楼前集合原地待命 离楼远点
or hostages will continue to fall from the sky.
不然人质会继续从天而降
Tell Detective Paul to have his men stand down.
让Paul警探叫他的人待命吧
Bravo team, stand down.
B队 待命
All clear.
可以了
Done. What else?
照做了 还有什么要求?
We'd like three v-tols on the roof standing by, clear airspace from here to the border,
我们需要三架v-tols在楼顶待命 从这到边境要净空
and finally, I'd like one fission igniter delivered to me, please.
最后 再给我送台核裂变点火器来
That's military-grade technology. I don't have that authority.
那是军用科技 我没有那个权限
Well, then I suggest you contact someone who does.
那建议你跟有权限的人取得联系
Facial recognition identified.
面部识别成功
Now, you listen to me, Lucas, if you want me to cooperate with you,
听我说 Lucas 想让我跟你合作
I need you to cooperate with me.
你也得跟我合作
How many hostages do you have?
你们劫持了多少人质?
More than enough to end your career
足够毁掉你职业生涯的
if they die.
如果他们都送命的话
You have 43 minutes.
给你43分钟的时间
Set the timer for 43 minutes, and get me Rudy Lom.
43分钟倒计时 然后给我接Rudy Lom
Hello? Are you there?
喂? 你还在吗?
- Right here, Paige. - Is anyone coming?
- 在呢 Paige - 还有人会来吗?
You just hang tight. We're gonna be with you real soon.
你保持镇定 我们马上就跟你会合
- Did you hear the phone call? - Yeah, I did. Thank you.
- 你有听到那通电话吗? - 听到了 谢谢
Just hold on a second. I'll be right back.
稍等一下 一会再跟你通话
Is a fission igniter as bad as I think it is?
核裂变点火器真有那么严重?
It's a trigger mechanism for a large explosive device.
那是巨型爆炸装置的点燃器
- Megaton level. - Megaton.
- 兆吨级的爆炸力 - 兆吨
Paige, you there?
Paige 还在吗?
Can you tell me how many hostages they've got up there?
能告诉我他们劫持了多少人质吗?
25 or so.
25个左右吧
At least in this room. It's hard for me to see.
至少这个房间是这么多 我看不太清
You're doing great, Paige.
你做得非常棒 Paige
- How's your sister? - This is all my fault.
- 你妹妹现在怎么样? - 都是我的错
She wouldn't be here if it wasn't for me.
要不是我的话 她就不会在这了
She's visiting from out of town.
她是从外地来的
She just stopped by to have lunch...
只是来这边吃个午饭
and now she's all alone.
现在她一个人在那
Paige, can you tell me how many gunmen there are?
Paige 能告诉我拿枪的匪徒有几名吗?
People keep coming and going; I don't know.
他们来来去去的 我也不大清楚
Five... six, at least.
至少有五六个吧
But there were more.
但刚才有更多来着
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
对不起 我不敢细看
I'm so scared.
我太害怕了
Paige, you ever been ice fishing?
Paige 你有在冰上钓过鱼吗?
- No. - When I was 11 years old,
- 没有 - 我11岁的时候
my dad took me ice fishing to Lake McFarland.
爸爸带我去McFarland湖冰上钓鱼
We were coming back, and all of a sudden
我们正准备往回走 突然之间
the ice cracked, and I went right under.
冰面裂开 我掉进了冰窟窿里
I couldn't see, I couldn't breathe.
什么都看不到 没有办法呼吸
I thought I was gonna die.
我以为自己要死了
The water was so cold, it was like thousands of needles
湖水特别冷 像是千万根冰针
stinging every part of my body.
刺着身体的每个部分
And then my dad jumped in,
然后我爸爸跳了进来
and he grabbed me and started dragging me back to shore.
他抓住我 把我朝岸上拖
Are you trying to put her to sleep?
你在哄她睡觉吗?
And even though we were still in a lot of danger,
尽管当时还是很危险
I felt safe. I felt like...
可我却觉得很安全 感觉就像
everything was gonna be okay, because I wasn't alone.
一定不会有意外似的 因为我不是一个人
Paige...
Paige
you're not alone.
你不是一个人
I'm with you.
有我陪着你
Everything is gonna be okay.
不会有任何意外的
Do you believe me?
相信我吗?
- Yeah, I do. - All right, good girl.
- 相信 - 好 好姑娘
You just hang in there.
你就呆在那
Yeah. Paul.
是我 Paul
- Any sign of Kennex and Dorian? - Uh, nothing so far.
- 有发现Kennex和Dorian吗? - 暂时还没有
Keep your men back, but I want drones and spotters on every window and exit.
让你的人撤吧 但每扇窗 每个出口 都要有无人机和探测器
- I want to know what's happening with my men. - Yeah, you got it, Captain.
- 我要知道我手下的情况 - 明白 队长
There's no way I can get a fission igniter.
我根本拿不到什么核裂变点火器
What if there was a way to give them what they wanted
如果我有办法给他们提供这个
and stall them at the same time?
同时又能拖住他们呢?
- What have you got? - I could build a replica.
- 你有什么主意? - 我可以做一个假的
What if they can spot a fake?
如果他们能识别出来呢?
I can make one that will pass a scan.
我可以做一个能通过检测的
If they test it out or try and use it immediately, then we're out of luck.
但如果他们当场试验 或者立刻要用的话 就只能算我们运气不好了
That's risk we'll have to take. Let's get started.
这个险值得冒 行动吧
- Captain? - Yep?
- 队长? - 什么事?
Lucas Vincent... he's a high-level operative in the Holy Reclamation Army,
Lucas Vincent是神圣开拓部队的高级头目
a decentralized network of terrorist cells with anti-Western bias and a history of hostage taking,
是几个小恐怖组织的松散联合 这些组织都反西方 还劫持过人质
none of them ending well.
下场也都不好
Last August they took over an embassy near Tokyo.
去年八月他们占领了东京附近一座大使馆
Same MO... they enter with force,
作案方式一样 先武力进入
drew the attention of the media and law enforcement
吸引媒体和执法人员的注意
using human hostages as collateral for their demands.
用人质做筹码提出要求
- What happened? - They facilitated the release of several of their comrades.
- 他们提了什么要求? - 要求释放几名他们的人
Once they got what they wanted, they released the hostages.
目的达成之后 就把人质释放了
But they're not afraid to take lives... including their own.
但他们杀人毫不手软 包括自己人
You know, everyone trips on stairs,
大家都会被楼梯绊倒
and it's calculated to occur in one in every 2,222 occasions.
机率是2222分之一
That's very interesting.
挺有意思的
- You know what would be interesting, John? - What?
- 知道怎样才真有意思吗 John? - 什么?
If you told me that ice fishing story again.
你再跟我讲一遍那个冰上钓鱼的故事
If you want to get in shape, we can run the O-course every weekend.
你要想恢复身材的话 我们可以每周末都照那个路线跑一圈
O- can we?
哦 是吗?
Let's split up.
分头行动
Dorian, you okay?
Dorian 你还好吗?
John, get over here.
John 过来
Floor's clear.
这里暂时安全
You okay?
你还好吧?
You took one to the head.
头部中了一枪
Yeah, ricochet.
嗯 只是跳弹
- Whatcha got? - I'm not sure.
- 你手上是什么? - 我也不确定
But there's writing on it. "Start. "
- 这上面有字 - "启动"
- Start? - Start.
- 启动? - 启动
You I.D.'d him?
能确认他的身份吗?
His name is Michael Demerais. He's a member of the Holy Reclamation Army.
他叫Michael Demerais 神圣开拓部队成员
So they're behind this.
原来背后是他们
Maybe not.
也未必
It's a facemaker.
是面部改变器
So who's this guy?
那这个人又是谁?
His name is Gregor Stone. He has a few priors for armed robbery.
他叫Gregor Stone 有持枪抢劫的前科
Why would they impersonate members of a radical organization?
他们为什么要假扮极端组织分子呢?
What's wrong?
怎么了?
My dynamic voltage scaling has been damaged by the bullet.
我的动态电压缩放装置被破坏了
You want to say that a little less complicated?
你还可以说得更复杂一点
I won't be able to walk in five minutes.
五分钟之后我会连路都走不了
- Where are our v-tols? - I'm working on it.
- 我们的V-tols在哪呢? - 我已经在安排了
Based on the frequency at which these transmit...
根据发射信号的频率
I detect seven facemakers in the building.
我探测到这栋楼里还有七个同样的装置
If they hide their identities, why not just wear a mask?
要隐瞒身份的话 怎么不用面罩呢?
- Why pretend to be something else? - That's a good question.
- 为什么还要假扮其他人? - 问得好
All right.
来吧
Let's try and fix you.
我们来把你修好
How does it look?
看起来怎么样?
Yeah, it's, uh, totally fine.
看着没什么事
- You can hardly see it. - Okay.
- 你基本看不到对吧 - 嗯
So, what do I do?
我需要怎么做?
All right, there's a magenta colored tendon.
那有块洋红色的肌腱
I need you to cut it.
你把那个剪断
All right, is... is that thing clean?
那个...那个东西干净吗?
- Of course it is. - Are you sure?
- 当然 - 你确定?
Positive.
非常确定
Damn it.
我++
- I said magenta. - It was magenta.
- 我说洋红 - 是洋红啊
- I said magenta. That was lavender. - The hell's magenta?
- 我说洋红 你剪了淡紫 - 毛的洋红
There's 50 shades of purple in there.
这有50种紫色
I'm telling you, that was the lavender one.
我正在跟你说啊 你刚剪了淡紫
- No, no. Okay, wait a minute. - What?
- 不 别 等一下 - 又怎么
- What are you doing with that? - Gotta cut the wire.
- 你拿那个东西做什么? - 剪线啊
- That's not going inside of my head. - I'm your partner, trust me.
- 别拿那玩意儿碰我的头 - 我是你的搭档 相信我
If Rudy were here,
Rudy要是在这的话
he'd have a really big issue with you right now.
他非跟你没完不行
- John... - Look, it could always be worse.
- John - 听着 只有更糟没有最糟
- John, the statistics... - You're going to be fine.
- John 那些数据... - 你不会有事的
Dorian?
Dorian?
Please stop looking at me like that.
别再那样子盯着我了
You have five minutes to deliver the decoy fission device.
你还剩五分钟可以完成这个假点火装置
I'm working as fast as I can.
我动作已经很快了
Four minutes, 45 seconds.
4分45秒
You can't put a clock on perfection.
你还能催得再紧点么
Clearly someone was rushing when they designed your manners chip.
那人设计你的行为芯片时太赶了吧
- John, are you there? - I can hear you, Paige.
- John 你还在吗? - 我听到了 Paige
They've moved.
他们换位置了
They keep going to a corner window...
一直往角落一扇窗户那边去...
- doing something. - What are they doing?
- 像在做什么事 - 他们在做什么?
I don't know.
我不知道
My sister... she's crying.
我妹妹...她在哭
And one of the guards, he keeps looking at her.
有个人 他一直盯着我妹妹
Look, I promise I'll get to you soon, Paige.
听我说 我保证很快过去 Paige
What's your sister's name?
你妹妹叫什么名字?
Jenna.
Jenna
- Jenna? - Her middle name's Gertrude.
- Jenna? - 她中名叫Gertrude
- Ooh, that's rough. - What's yours?
- 哦 情况还真糟 - 你的呢?
Oh, no. No, no, we're not doing that.
哦 这个可不能问哦
Come on, tell me.
告诉我吧
All right, but you better not tell anyone, okay?
好吧 但你不许告诉其他人 好吧?
Police orders.
警局有规定
It's Reginald.
是Reginald
My dad was a big Elton John fan.
我爸爸是Elton John的粉丝
Who?
谁?
Elton John. He's an old-time singer.
Elton John 以前的一位歌手
Apparently, his real name was Reginald.
然后他的中名就叫Reginald
You okay?
感觉怎么样?
Gross.
有点简陋
- But good. - Something's happening.
- 但还不错 - 发生了什么事
Get over here and help.
来搭把手
One of the gunmen,
有一名匪徒
- he's hurt. - Who shot you?
- 受伤了 - 谁打伤你的?
There are two men in the building.
楼里还有俩人
- Cops? - I don't know.
- 条子? - 不知道
Where's Gregor?
Gregor呢?
- We got separated. - Do you want us to look for him?
- 我们分开了 - 要去找找他吗?
No.
不用
Put more men on the stairwell. No one gets up on this floor.
楼梯口多去几个人 别放任何人进这层楼
Go. You, go.
快 你去吧
John, they know you're in the building.
John 他们知道你们还在楼里了
They sent a couple guys with giant guns to guard the stairs.
还派了几个人端着重型枪去楼梯口守着
Even if you do get up here, how are you gonna get in?
就算你们能上来 要怎么进来呢?
Trust me, Paige.
相信我 Paige
We'll find a way to get to you.
我们会有办法去救你的
I'm disappointed in you, Captain Maldonado.
我对你很是失望啊 Maldonado队长
I thought we were getting along so well.
我怎么觉得挺好的啊
- I don't know what you're talking about. - I said no cops.
- 不知道你在说什么 - 我说不准有警察在
I pulled my men back.
我把人都撤了啊
The only people I have there are conducting the evacuation, outside the building.
只留了负责疏散的人 而且还在楼外
Then how do you explain the two cops
那你怎么解释那俩条子呢
my men just killed downstairs?
我的人刚在楼下干掉他们
He's bluffing.
他在虚张声势
I don't know what men you killed, but they weren't mine.
我不清楚你杀了什么人 但肯定不是我的人
We made a deal. I get you what you want, no one else dies.
我们不是达成协议了么 我提供你要的 你不准再杀人
When do I get my fission ignitor?
我的核裂变点火器什么时候送来?
It's on its way, ten minutes or less.
在路上了 10分钟之内就到
Great. Every minute longer
很好 因为每超过一分钟
is another body you'll be scraping off the pavement.
你们就得从人行道上多拖一具尸体
Keep your mouth shut.
嘴巴给我闭起来
John?
John?
I'm going out there. I can't leave Jenna alone.
我要出去了 我不能留Jenna一个人
- Paige, that's a bad idea. - I have to. I have to.
- Paige 这样不行 - 我必须这样 必须
- We're a few floors away. - She needs me.
- 我们还有几层楼就到了 - 她需要我
I need her.
我也需要她
If we're gonna die...
如果我们不得不死
...I want to be with her.
我想跟她死在一起
She's my sister.
她是我妹妹
Now is my only chance to blend in without anyone seeing me.
这是我唯一能趁他们不注意溜进去的机会
- Paige, just stay where you are. - I'll leave my phone open.
- Paige 你就呆在原地 - 我把手机开着
- You'll be able to hear what's going on. - Paige, it's too risky.
- 这样你还能听到里面的情况 - Paige 这太冒险了
- Listen to me, just stay put. - I have to.
- 听我说 你先别动 - 我必须这样
- please - Paige, please, just listen to me. Paige.
- 拜托了 - Paige 你听我的 Paige
Paige, are you there? Paige?
Paige 你还在吗 Paige?
I think I can do that.
交给我吧
I'm here.
我来了
It'll be okay.
不会有事的
Detective Paul?
Paul警探?
- Copy. - The ignitor is ready for delivery.
在 点火器可以运送了
- Come on. - Come on, come on, speed it up.
快 快点
- It's good to go, sir. - Okay, waiting on your order.
- 准备完毕 长官 - 只等您下令了
Send it.
送上去吧
Excuse me.
不好意思
I have to go to the bathroom.
我想上个厕所
You're not going to make me pee on the floor, are you?
总不能让我尿在这吧?
You've got 30 seconds.
给你半分钟
Hey, boss...
嘿 头儿
we're getting another delivery.
又有东西送来了
The drone's coming.
无人机来了
We had an agreement, Lucas. We've operated in good faith here.
我们有共识 Lucas 我们也已经表达了诚意
I believe in honoring a deal.
我这人说到做到
Stand by.
你们等着
I'll let you know how we're gonna release the hostages.
我会让你知道我们怎样释放人质的
Let's hope they buy it.
希望能骗过他们吧
Send the message to the other crew now.
给他们那队传信息吧
They should be ready. It's time to wind this up.
他们应该早准备好了 也该结束了
- What other crew? - Maybe there are more of them in the building.
- 什么他们那队? - 可能楼里不只有他们
- Maybe they're outside the building. - But the jammer's still on. If they have people outside,
- 也可能楼外还有一队人 - 干扰装置还开着 就算外面还有人
they wouldn't be able to talk to each other.
他们也无法通信啊
Unless they were talking some other way.
除非他们用其他办法联系
"Start. "
"启动"
They must be using it as some sort of point-to-point communication
他们一定是用这个来进行点对点联系的
- with someone in proximity - of the building. - Paige said the man in charge...
- 与离这栋楼不远的人 - Paige说匪徒的头目
kept going to the window.
一直往窗户那边去
I didn't think they'd come through.
他们不会就这样乖乖就范的
What if there's a tracking device?
如果里面有追踪装置怎么办?
We're not taking it anyway.
反正我们也不带走
It doesn't matter.
没关系的
He doesn't want the tech. That doesn't make sense.
他不想要那个吗 这说不通啊
Why take hostages and negotiate for tech you don't want?
为什么要劫持人质 谈判要求自己不需要的东西呢?
Maybe it's a diversion.
也许这只是个幌子
Yeah, but for what?
嗯 那真正的意图呢?
Are there any targets of value in the adjacent buildings?
周围的大楼有什么高价值的东西吗?
The only target of any value is a precious metal weigh station specializing in palladium.
唯一有价值的 就是一个 专门称量钯的稀有金属称量站
It's a heist.
这是抢劫
Palladium. That would make all this worthwhile.
钯 那这一切就都值得了
(10 min)
(10分钟)
Wrap it up. We're out of here in ten.
都装起来 10分钟之后撤
Hang in there, Daniel.
再坚持一下 Daniel
When this is over, we'll all be on a beach somewhere,
干完这一票 我们就可以找个海滩退隐
you'll be as good as new.
你不会有任何事的
I need a doctor.
我需要医生
Soon.
很快
What's that beeping?
那哔哔声怎么回事?
You and the guys pick three hostages.
拉三个人质出来
Why?
干嘛?
We may need insurance. Let's pack it up.
我们需要筹码 收拾吧
(LIGHTBOMB AUDIO DETECTED) John, they've activated a light bomb.
John 他们启动了一枚光弹
They're gonna kill the hostages.
他们打算把人质都杀掉
- What are you doing? - Sticking to the plan. We're going up.
- 你做什么? - 按原计划继续上楼
John, they know we're here.
John 他们知道我们在楼里
They're expecting us to come up the stairs.
正等着我们上去呢
We won't make it to the 25th floor alive.
我们没办法活着到达25楼的
You heard him. We have no choice.
你听到他的话了 我们没得选
I don't have a choice.
是我没得选
People's lives are in jeopardy.
有人生命受到了威胁
Dorian, You've been shot. Your head's full of bubble gum. You can't do this alone.
Dorian 你中枪了 头用口香糖处理过 你一个人不行的
- I have to. - Then I'm coming with you.
- 我必须这样 - 那我跟你一起去
You can't.
不行
I'm designed to do this, John.
我被开发出来就是为了这种情况 John
It's time.
到时间了
(Identify subject Vicent Lucas) Jenna... why don't you come with me.
Jenna 你跟我走
No, no, no. Don't you touch her.
不 不要 你别碰她
Don't you touch her. Take me!
不许你碰她 我跟你走
Let her go! I will shoot you!
放手! 不然我开枪了!
- No, no! Take me! No, leave her! - I will shoot you!
- 不 不要 让我去吧 留下她 - 我开枪了!
Take me! Please! Me!
让我去吧 求你了
Police! Get down!
警察 都趴下!
What's your name?
你叫什么名字?
I've never killed a man I didn't know.
我从来不杀不知道名字的人
But then again...
话又说回来
you're not a man.
你好像不是人
Are you?
对吗?
- Nice of you to show up, Gregor. - Where the hell have you been?
- 你可算出现了 Gregor - 跑哪去了?
We thought you were dead.
我们还以为你死了
- Maldonado? - John?
- Maldonado? - John?
The hostages are secure. The whole thing is a palladium heist.
人质已经安全了 匪徒的目标是那些钯
Shut it off... now!
快关闭干扰装置 马上关闭
They got us to block the alarm system.
他们是想让我们关闭警报系统
Turn the jammer off!
快把干扰装置关掉!
Detective Paul, turn off the jammer now!
Paul警探 把干扰装置关掉!
Shut it off.
关掉
Let's go.
撤
Thank you.
谢谢
John?
John?
You must be Paige.
你一定是Paige了
- Thank you. - No. Thank you.
- 谢谢你 - 不 是我要谢谢你
You were very brave.
你表现得很勇敢
You helped save a lot of lives today.
你帮我们救了很多人
Where's your partner?
你搭档呢?
Oh, he's, uh...
呃 他...
he's getting patched up.
他正在处理受损的地方
John, this is my sister. This is Jenna.
John 这是我妹妹 Jenna
Jenna, it's a pleasure to meet you. I've heard a lot about you.
Jenna 见到你很高兴 听你姐姐说了不少你的事
I'm glad you're okay.
很高兴你没事
Thanks.
谢谢
I've got some intel on the perps.
查到些匪徒的信息
Guy behind it all was Gerald Leighton.
策划这起抢劫的人是 Gerald Leighton
We linked him and his men to four high-value robberies in the last two years.
过去的两年里 这一伙人进行了四起高额抢劫
Using police jamming protocol to initiate a palladium heist.
利用警方启动干扰装置 以此为掩护去劫钯
- Pretty elaborate for a bunch of thieves. - It's going to be a paperwork nightmare.
- 一群毛贼竟然能如此精心策划 - 这报告写起来绝对会是噩梦啊
And I thought you had come down here to thank me.
我还以为你是来谢谢我的
For what? Doing your job?
谢你什么? 做了自己的本职工作吗?
Just for the record, I did tell you to get out of the building, right?
为准确起见 我有命令你离开大楼 对吧?
I swear, all I heard was static.
我只听到了滋滋的干扰声
Oi! I've got a bone to pick with you, Detective.
喂 我对你有不满啊
Chewing gum? Really?
口香糖吗 啊?
Would you fix a race car with chewing gum?
你会用口香糖修赛车吗?
Uh, yeah, if it was busted, and I need to win a race.
会啊 如果车故障了 我又必须赢得比赛的话
He'll need extensive diagnostics.
他需要进一步检测
Ah, that can wait.
那个以后再说
Come on, let's go get some noodles.
走吧 去吃碗面
You are aware that I don't eat.
你知道我不吃东西的
Perfect. I'm buying. Let's roll.
正好 我买单 还省钱 走吧
Well, I'll just wait here, shall I?
那我就在这等了啊
Thank you for what you did back there.
谢谢你那样做
Don't mention it.
提这个做什么
Besides, no one messes with my coffee warmer.
哪能让别人找我咖啡加热器的麻烦啊
Hey, John, you know that story you told Paige,
嘿 John 你告诉Paige那个故事
when you fell through the ice as a kid?
就是你小时候掉进冰窟窿那事
When that gun was pointed at my head, I felt something similar.
那把枪指着我的头时 我也有跟你当时一样的感受
I- I didn't want to die.
我不想死
I know it's not the same with me, but...
我知道我不一样...
Hey, dead is dead.
嘿 死了就什么都没有了
Yeah.
嗯
I suppose so.
是吧
Why don't you chuck some music on?
来点音乐呗?
Elton John, huh? You heard me, didn't you?
Elton John? 你当时听到我讲了吧?
Don't. Don't. Please, don't do that.
别嚎了 快停下吧
Whatever you say, Reginald.
随你啊 Reginald
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入